<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<example>
<description>
<english>A simple ANN example running on a single device</english>
<simplified_chinese>一个在单一设备上运行的简单人工神经网示例</simplified_chinese>
<traditional_chinese>一個在單一設備上運行的簡單人工神經網示例</traditional_chinese>
<spanish>Un ejemplo de una red neuronal artificial simple que se ejecuta en un solo dispositivo</spanish>
</description>
<application>
<applicationName>A Simple ANN</applicationName>
<applicationPkgName>com.SimpANN.sMachine</applicationPkgName>
<applicationWorkingFolder>SimpANN1Machine</applicationWorkingFolder>
<applicationVersionStr>1.0.0.1882</applicationVersionStr>
<applicationVersionCode>1882</applicationVersionCode>
<functionInfo>
<name>mfpexample::single_machine::run_ANN</name>
<description>This is a simple ANN example running on a single device. There are 8 nodes in the ANN. This program has no parameter. When it starts, it first sends 200 training data to set up ANN weight parameters. After that more data are sent to ANN to identify and group. Once the whole process finishes, a chart is plotted to visualize the result. 
这是一个人工神经网的简单例子。这个人工神经网有8个节点。运行这个例子的程序没有参数。这个程序首先发送200组训练数据训练这个人工神经网络以设置权重参数，然后发送更多的数据给这个人工神经网络进行识别。在所有的过程结束之后，该程序会把结果用图形的方式显示出来。
</description>
<includesOptionalParam>FALSE</includesOptionalParam>
<parameters>
</parameters>
</functionInfo>
<helpInfo></helpInfo>
</application>
<sourceFiles>
<sourceFile>example.mfps</sourceFile>
</sourceFiles>
<apkFile>ann_1machine.apk</apkFile>
<info>
<english>This is a simple ANN example running on a single device. There are 8 nodes in the ANN. This program has no parameter. When it starts, it first sends 200 training data to set up ANN weight parameters. After that more data are sent to ANN to identify and group. Once the whole process finishes, a chart is plotted to visualize the result. </english>
<simplified_chinese>这是一个人工神经网的简单例子。这个人工神经网有8个节点。运行这个例子的程序没有参数。这个程序首先发送200组训练数据训练这个人工神经网络以设置权重参数，然后发送更多的数据给这个人工神经网络进行识别。在所有的过程结束之后，该程序会把结果用图形的方式显示出来。</simplified_chinese>
<traditional_chinese>這是一個人工神經網的簡單例子。這個人工神經網有8個節點。運行這個例子的程序沒有參數。這個程序首先發送200組訓練數據訓練這個人工神經網絡以設置權重參數，然後發送更多的數據給這個人工神經網絡進行識別。在所有的過程結束之後，該程序會把結果用圖形的方式顯示出來。</traditional_chinese>
<spanish>Este es un ejemplo simple de una red neuronal artificial. Esta red neuronal artificial tiene 8 nodos. El programa para ejecutar este ejemplo no tiene parámetros. Este programa primero envía 200 conjuntos de datos de entrenamiento para entrenar a la red neuronal artificial para que establezca los parámetros de peso y luego envía más datos a la red neuronal artificial para su reconocimiento. Una vez finalizados todos los procesos, el programa mostrará los resultados gráficamente.</spanish>
</info>
</example>
