<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<example>
<description>
<english>A hungry snake game for multiplayers</english>
<simplified_chinese>一个多玩家贪吃蛇游戏</simplified_chinese>
<traditional_chinese>一個多玩家貪吃蛇遊戲</traditional_chinese>
<spanish>Un juego de serpiente hambrienta para varios jugadores</spanish>
</description>
<application>
<applicationName>Hungry Snake Parallel</applicationName>
<applicationPkgName>com.HSnakes.Parallel</applicationPkgName>
<applicationWorkingFolder>HunSnakeParallel</applicationWorkingFolder>
<applicationVersionStr>1.0.1.1883</applicationVersionStr>
<applicationVersionCode>1883</applicationVersionCode>
<functionInfo>
<name> gdi_test::game_test::oo_hungry_snake_parallel::run </name>
<description>This is a hungry snake game for multi-players. At most 4 people (using 4 different devices) can play together. The entry point of this game is the run function. This run function takes no parameter. Player needs to input local IP address (i.e. player's device IP address) and remote server IP address if not the first player when the game starts. Remote server can be any of the other players who have already joined the game. Player can control the snake moving direction by tapping the Left, Top, Right and Bottom button. Player can also achieve the same thing by dragging/dropping mouse or swipping the finger on the non-button area of the display window. If player's snake eats a piece of food, its length increases. If player's snake hits the body of another snake or itself, the player loses.
这是一款适合多人游戏的贪吃蛇游戏。最多可以有4个人（使用4种不同的设备）一起玩。该游戏的切入点是run函数。此函数没有参数。游戏开始时，玩家需要输入玩家的设备IP地址。如果玩家不是第一个，就还需要输入前面已经加入游戏的另一个玩家的IP地址。玩家可以通过点击“左”，“上”，“右”和“下”按钮来控制蛇的移动方向。玩家还可以通过在显示窗口的非按钮区域上拖放鼠标或滑动手指来实现相同的目的。如果玩家的蛇吃了一块食物，它的长度就会增加。如果玩家的蛇碰到了另一条蛇或者它自己的身体，则玩家会输。
</description>
<includesOptionalParam>FALSE</includesOptionalParam>
<parameters>
</parameters>
</functionInfo>
<helpInfo></helpInfo>
</application>
<sourceFiles>
<sourceFile>oo_hungry_snake_parallel.mfps</sourceFile>
</sourceFiles>
<assets>
<asset>food.png</asset>
<asset>eatfood.wav</asset>
<asset>hitothers.wav</asset>
</assets>
<apkFile>hungry_snake_parallel.apk</apkFile>
<info>
<english>This is a hungry snake game for multi-players. It is for fun and pleasure. It can have 4 players at most. The source file is oo_hungry_snake_parallel.mfps. There are two wave files to mimic the sounds of eating food and hitting other snakes. All the files have been zipped in an attachment to share by email.</english>
<simplified_chinese>这是一个多玩家贪吃蛇的小游戏。它最多可以有四个玩家一起玩。本游戏的源代码位于文件hungry_snake_parallel.mfps中。此外，本游戏还包括两个声音文件用于模拟吃食物和撞到其他蛇的声音。如果玩家共享本游戏的代码，游戏相关文件会被打入一个压缩包中通过email发给别人。</simplified_chinese>
<traditional_chinese>這是一個多玩家貪吃蛇的小遊戲。它最多可以有四个玩家一起玩。遊戲的源代碼位於檔案hungry_snake_parallel.mfps中。此外，本遊戲還包括兩個聲音檔案用於模擬吃食物和撞到其他蛇的聲音。如果玩家共享本遊戲的代碼，遊戲相關檔案會被打入一個壓縮包中通過email發給別人。</traditional_chinese>
<spanish>Este es un juego de serpientes multijugador. Se puede jugar con hasta cuatro jugadores. El código fuente del juego se encuentra en el archivo oo_hungry_snake_parallel.mfps. Además, el juego también incluye dos archivos de sonido para simular el sonido de comer y golpear a otras serpientes. Si el jugador comparte el código de este juego, los archivos relacionados con el juego se colocarán en un paquete comprimido y se enviarán a otros por correo electrónico.</spanish>
</info>
</example>
