<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<example>
<description>
<english>Chinese Chess on 2 devices</english>
<simplified_chinese>双机对战中国象棋</simplified_chinese>
<traditional_chinese>雙機對戰中國象棋</traditional_chinese>
<spanish>Ajedrez chino en 2 dispositivos</spanish>
</description>
<application>
<applicationName>双机对战中国象棋</applicationName>
<applicationPkgName>co.cchess.twodevices</applicationPkgName>
<applicationWorkingFolder>cchess2dev</applicationWorkingFolder>
<applicationVersionStr>1.1.1.1936</applicationVersionStr>
<applicationVersionCode>1936</applicationVersionCode>
<functionInfo>
<name> gdi_test::game_test::chinese_chess::main </name>
<description>这是一个由MFP语言开发的双机对战中国象棋的游戏。本游戏需要两个玩家，分别使用不同的安卓设备但运行同样的软件。玩这个游戏不需要中央服务器，两台安卓设备通过TCPIP协议或者基于电子邮件地址的WebRTC协议进行点对点的通信。如果使用TCPIP协议，必须保证至少一台设备能看见另外一台设备。能够看到对方的设备作为客户端发起连接，而对方设备作为服务端，两者之间可以存在NAT层。游戏启动时会显示本机的IP地址，先启动游戏的玩家（也就是服务端玩家）必须事先就告诉对方本机IP地址，然后后启动游戏的玩家（也就是客户端）输入第一个玩家的IP地址进行连接，如果连接成功游戏就开始。如果使用基于电子邮件地址的WebRTC协议进行点对点的通信，则可以实现远距离（几千公里）的象棋对战。启动游戏的流程和使用TCPIP协议相似，第一个玩家启动后等待第二个玩家启动并输入第一个玩家的电子邮件地址后进行连接。如果连接成功游戏就开始。但有一点和使用TCPIP协议不同的是，第一次使用WebRTC协议进行点对点的通信时需要设置本机的电子邮件地址。设置时需要输入邮件地址，密码（注意这个密码是用smtp和imap协议进行收发邮件时所使用的密码，它不见得和登录网页进行邮件查收所使用的密码一样）。如果是使用的微软outlook信箱，腾讯QQ信箱，yahoo邮箱或者谷歌gmail邮箱，则不用再输入其他的信息，否则还需要输入smtp和imap的服务器信息。除此之外，用户还需要确保自己的电子邮件已经打开了smtp和imap服务以及对方的邮件地址不会被放入黑名单（也就是对方的连接请求邮件不会被当作垃圾邮件）。使用WebRTC协议，仅仅需要交换两封邮件便可以建立连接，所以一般不会出现信号邮件被当作垃圾邮件丢弃的情况。但是，如果频繁地尝试连接，并且在尝试连接的过程中频繁地切换网络，有些邮件服务提供商，比如微软和谷歌，会怀疑是犯罪分子在偷发垃圾邮件，可能会暂时阻止玩家发送和接受邮件，需要用户登录网页进行确认。第一次使用WebRTC协议email邮箱服务端的设置会比较繁琐，但是设置成功后，就不需要再进行更改，两个距离遥远的玩家可以随时像身处同一房间一样进行象棋对战。由于使用了WebRTC的音频和视频通话的功能，玩家在对弈时还可以视频聊天。
This is a dual-player Chinese chess game developed by MFP programming language. This game requires two players, using different Android devices but running the same software. There is no need for a central server to play this game. Two Android devices communicate point-to-point through TCPIP protocol or WebRTC protocol based on email addresses. If you use the TCPIP protocol, the two devices are not required to sit in the same gateway. NAT layer in between is acceptable. When the game starts, the IP address of the device will be displayed. The player who starts the game first must tell the other party the IP address of the machine, and then the player who starts the game enters the IP address of the first player to connect. If the connection is built up successfully, the game will start. If you use the email address based WebRTC protocol for point-to-point communication, you can play with the other party thousands of kilometers away. The process to start the game is similar to using the TCPIP protocol. After the first player starts, wait for the second player to start and enter the email address of the first player to connect. If the connection is successful, the game will start. But one thing is different from TCPIP. The first time you use the WebRTC protocol for peer-to-peer communication, you need to set the e-mail address of the machine. You need to enter the email address and password in the setup (note that this is the password used when sending and receiving emails with smtp and imap protocols, it is not necessarily the same as the password used to login the webmail). If you are using Microsoft Outlook mailbox, Tencent QQ mailbox, yahoo mail or Google gmail mailbox, you do not need to enter other information, otherwise you need to enter smtp and imap server information. In addition, users also need to make sure that smtp and imap services have been turned on and that the other party's email address will not be blacklisted, which means the other party's signal emails will not be treated as spam). When using an email address for peer-to-peer communication for the first time, some mail service providers, such as Microsoft and Google, will detect the device sending the email. If it is a new device, it may temporarily block the sending, requiring the user to login webmail to confirm. Therefore, the first time to use the WebRTC protocol setting will be more cumbersome, but after setting is done successfully, there is no need to change it. Two players who are far away can play chess against each other as if they are in the same room at any time. Furthermore, this version of the game has started to support video and voice communiction. As such players can chat with each other when they are playing the game.
</description>
<includesOptionalParam>FALSE</includesOptionalParam>
<parameters>
</parameters>
</functionInfo>
<helpInfo></helpInfo>
</application>
<sourceFiles>
<sourceFile>cchess.mfps</sourceFile>
</sourceFiles>
<assets>
<asset>badmove.wav</asset>
<asset>BlackBishop.png</asset>
<asset>BlackCannon.png</asset>
<asset>BlackGuard.png</asset>
<asset>BlackKing.png</asset>
<asset>BlackKnight.png</asset>
<asset>BlackPawn.png</asset>
<asset>BlackRook.png</asset>
<asset>CChessCheckerBoard.png</asset>
<asset>eatmove.wav</asset>
<asset>goodmove.wav</asset>
<asset>RedBishop.png</asset>
<asset>RedCannon.png</asset>
<asset>RedGuard.png</asset>
<asset>RedKing.png</asset>
<asset>RedKnight.png</asset>
<asset>RedPawn.png</asset>
<asset>RedRook.png</asset>
<asset>SelectedPiece.png</asset>
<asset>VoiceOn.png</asset>
<asset>VoiceOff.png</asset>
<asset>CameraOn.png</asset>
<asset>CameraOff.png</asset>
</assets>
<apkFile>cchess.apk</apkFile>
<info>
<english>This is a dual-player Chinese chess game developed by MFP programming language. This game requires two players, using different Android devices but running the same software. There is no need for a central server to play this game. Two Android devices communicate point-to-point through TCPIP protocol or WebRTC protocol based on email addresses. If you use the TCPIP protocol, you must ensure that the two devices can see each other, preferably in the same gateway to avoid being blocked by a firewall. When the game starts, the IP address of the device will be displayed. The player who starts the game first must tell the other party the IP address of the machine, and then the player who starts the game enters the IP address of the first player to connect. If the connection is built up successfully, the game will start. If you use the email address based WebRTC protocol for point-to-point communication, you can play with the other party thousands of kilometers away. The process to start the game is similar to using the TCPIP protocol. After the first player starts, wait for the second player to start and enter the email address of the first player to connect. If the connection is successful, the game will start. But one thing is different from TCPIP. The first time you use the WebRTC protocol for peer-to-peer communication, you need to set the e-mail address of the machine. You need to enter the email address and password in the setup (note that this is the password used when sending and receiving emails with smtp and imap protocols, it is not necessarily the same as the password used to login the webmail). If you are using Microsoft Outlook mailbox, Tencent QQ mailbox or Google gmail mailbox, you do not need to enter other information, otherwise you need to enter smtp and imap server information. In addition, users also need to make sure that smtp and imap services have been turned on and that the other party's email address will not be blacklisted, which means the other party's signal emails will not be treated as spam). When using an email address for peer-to-peer communication for the first time, some mail service providers, such as Microsoft and Google, will detect the device sending the email. If it is a new device, it may temporarily block the sending, requiring the user to login webmail to confirm. Therefore, the first time to use the WebRTC protocol setting will be more cumbersome, but after setting is done successfully, there is no need to change it. Two players who are far away can play chess against each other as if they are in the same room at any time.</english>
<simplified_chinese>这是一个由MFP语言开发的双机对战中国象棋的游戏。本游戏需要两个玩家，分别使用不同的安卓设备但运行同样的软件。玩这个游戏不需要中央服务器，两台安卓设备通过TCPIP协议或者基于电子邮件地址的WebRTC协议进行点对点的通信。如果使用TCPIP协议，必须保证两台设备能够相互可见，最好能够在同一网关内以免受到防火墙的阻隔。游戏启动时会显示本机的IP地址，先启动游戏的玩家必须告诉对方本机IP地址，然后后启动游戏的玩家输入第一个玩家的IP地址进行连接，如果连接成功游戏就开始。如果使用基于电子邮件地址的WebRTC协议进行点对点的通信，则可以实现远距离（几千公里）的象棋对战。启动游戏的流程和使用TCPIP协议相似，第一个玩家启动后等待第二个玩家启动并输入第一个玩家的电子邮件地址后进行连接。如果连接成功游戏就开始。但有一点和使用TCPIP协议不同的是，第一次使用WebRTC协议进行点对点的通信时需要设置本机的电子邮件地址。设置时需要输入邮件地址，密码（注意这个密码是用smtp和imap协议进行收发邮件时所使用的密码，它不见得和登录网页进行邮件查收所使用的密码一样）。如果是使用的微软outlook信箱，腾讯QQ信箱或者谷歌gmail邮箱，则不用再输入其他的信息，否则还需要输入smtp和imap的服务器信息。除此之外，用户还需要确保自己的电子邮件已经打开了smtp和imap服务以及对方的邮件地址不会被放入黑名单（也就是对方的连接请求邮件不会被当作垃圾邮件）。在第一次使用电子邮件地址进行点对点通信时，有些邮件服务提供商，比如微软和谷歌，会检测发送邮件的设备，如果是新设备，可能会暂时阻止发送，需要用户登录网页进行确认。第一次使用WebRTC协议设置会比较繁琐，但是设置成功后，就不需要再进行更改，两个距离遥远的玩家可以随时像身处同一房间一样进行象棋对战。</simplified_chinese>
<traditional_chinese>這是一個由MFP語言開發的雙機對戰中國象棋的遊戲。本遊戲需要兩個玩家，分別使用不同的安卓設備但運行同樣的軟件。玩這個遊戲不需要中央服務器，兩臺安卓設備通過TCPIP協議或者基於電子郵件地址的WebRTC協議進行點對點的通信。如果使用TCPIP協議，必須保證兩臺設備能夠相互可見，最好能夠在同一網關內以免受到防火墻的阻隔。遊戲啟動時會顯示本機的IP地址，先啟動遊戲的玩家必須告訴對方本機IP地址，然後後啟動遊戲的玩家輸入第一個玩家的IP地址進行連接，如果連接成功遊戲就開始。如果使用基於電子郵件地址的WebRTC協議進行點對點的通信，則可以實現遠距離（幾千公裏）的象棋對戰。啟動遊戲的流程和使用TCPIP協議相似，第一個玩家啟動後等待第二個玩家啟動並輸入第一個玩家的電子郵件地址後進行連接。如果連接成功遊戲就開始。但有一點和使用TCPIP協議不同的是，第一次使用WebRTC協議進行點對點的通信時需要設置本機的電子郵件地址。設置時需要輸入郵件地址，密碼（註意這個密碼是用smtp和imap協議進行收發郵件時所使用的密碼，它不見得和登錄網頁進行郵件查收所使用的密碼一樣）。如果是使用的微軟outlook信箱，騰訊QQ信箱或者谷歌gmail郵箱，則不用再輸入其他的信息，否則還需要輸入smtp和imap的服務器信息。除此之外，用戶還需要確保自己的電子郵件已經打開了smtp和imap服務以及對方的郵件地址不會被放入黑名單（也就是對方的連接請求郵件不會被當作垃圾郵件）。在第一次使用電子郵件地址進行點對點通信時，有些郵件服務提供商，比如微軟和谷歌，會檢測發送郵件的設備，如果是新設備，可能會暫時阻止發送，需要用戶登錄網頁進行確認。第一次使用WebRTC協議設置會比較繁瑣，但是設置成功後，就不需要再進行更改，兩個距離遙遠的玩家可以隨時像身處同一房間一樣進行象棋對戰。</traditional_chinese>
<spanish>Este es un juego de ajedrez chino para dos jugadores desarrollado por el lenguaje de programación MFP. Este juego requiere dos jugadores, usando diferentes dispositivos Android pero ejecutando el mismo software. No es necesario un servidor central para jugar a este juego. Dos dispositivos Android se comunican punto a punto a través del protocolo TCPIP o el protocolo WebRTC basado en direcciones de correo electrónico. Si usa el protocolo TCPIP, debe asegurarse de que los dos dispositivos puedan verse entre sí, preferiblemente en la misma puerta de enlace para evitar ser bloqueados por un firewall. Cuando comience el juego, se mostrará la dirección IP del dispositivo. El jugador que comienza el juego primero debe decirle a la otra parte la dirección IP de la máquina, y luego el jugador que comienza el juego ingresa la dirección IP del primer jugador en conectarse. Si la conexión se establece correctamente, se iniciará el juego. Si utiliza el protocolo WebRTC basado en la dirección de correo electrónico para la comunicación punto a punto, puede jugar con la otra parte a miles de kilómetros de distancia. El proceso para iniciar el juego es similar a usar el protocolo TCPIP. Después de que comience el primer jugador, espere a que comience el segundo jugador e ingrese la dirección de correo electrónico del primer jugador que se conectará. Si la conexión es exitosa, se iniciará el juego. Pero una cosa es diferente de TCPIP. La primera vez que utilice el protocolo WebRTC para la comunicación de igual a igual, debe configurar la dirección de correo electrónico de la máquina. Debe ingresar la dirección de correo electrónico y la contraseña en la configuración (tenga en cuenta que esta es la contraseña que se usa al enviar y recibir correos electrónicos con los protocolos smtp e imap, no es necesariamente la misma que la contraseña que se usa para iniciar sesión en el correo web). Si está utilizando el buzón de correo de Microsoft Outlook, el buzón de correo de Tencent QQ o el buzón de correo de Google gmail, no es necesario que ingrese otra información; de lo contrario, debe ingresar la información del servidor smtp e imap. Además, los usuarios también deben asegurarse de que los servicios smtp e imap estén activados y que la dirección de correo electrónico de la otra parte no se incluirá en la lista negra, lo que significa que los correos electrónicos de señal de la otra parte no se tratarán como spam). Al usar una dirección de correo electrónico para la comunicación entre pares por primera vez, algunos proveedores de servicios de correo, como Microsoft y Google, detectarán el dispositivo que envía el correo electrónico. Si es un dispositivo nuevo, puede bloquear temporalmente el envío, lo que requiere que el usuario inicie sesión en el correo web para confirmar. Por lo tanto, la primera vez que utilice la configuración del protocolo WebRTC será más engorrosa, pero una vez que la configuración se haya realizado correctamente, no es necesario cambiarla. Dos jugadores que están lejos pueden jugar al ajedrez entre sí como si estuvieran en la misma habitación en cualquier momento.</spanish>
</info>
</example>
