<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<example>
<description>
<english>A rabbit jumping game</english>
<simplified_chinese>一个超级小白兔的游戏</simplified_chinese>
<traditional_chinese>一個超級小白兔的遊戲</traditional_chinese>
<spanish>Un super conejo juego</spanish>
</description>
<application>
<applicationName>Super rabbit game Example</applicationName>
<applicationPkgName>com.cyzapps.SuperRab</applicationPkgName><!-- In play store, it is pom.cyzapps.SuperRab -->
<applicationWorkingFolder>SuperRab</applicationWorkingFolder>
<applicationVersionStr>1.0.0.1805</applicationVersionStr>
<applicationVersionCode>1709</applicationVersionCode>
<functionInfo>
<name> :: gdi_test::game_test::super_bunny::run </name>
<description>This is a super rabbit game. It has four levels. The entry point of this game is the run function. This function takes zero parameter. Player can control the rabbit jumping direction by dragging and gliding finger or mouse. However, because of the gravity, the rabbit always jumps more downward than moving direction of finger (or mouse). When the rabbit jumps from the left cliff, it has to avoid the carnivores. However, when the rabbit arrives at the right cliff, it turns to a super rabbit and it can eat the carnivores. After the super rabbit jumps back, player passes one level.
这是一个超级小白兔的游戏。它有四关，它的入口函数是run函数。run函数没有参数。玩家通过滑动手指或鼠标来控制小白兔跳动的方向，但要注意，由于重力的缘故，小白兔跳动的方向相对于手指或鼠标滑动的方向总是偏下。当小白兔从左边的悬崖开始起跳的时候，需要避免跳到食肉动物的格子里被吃掉，但是当小白兔跳到右边悬崖后吃到胡萝卜就会变成超级小白兔，它向回跳时，就能够吃食肉动物。当超级小白兔跳回左边悬崖，玩家就通过了这一关。</description>
<includesOptionalParam>FALSE</includesOptionalParam>
<parameters>
</parameters>
</functionInfo>
<helpInfo></helpInfo>
</application>
<sourceFiles>
<sourceFile>super_bunny.mfps</sourceFile>
</sourceFiles>
<assets>
<asset>background.png</asset>
<asset>beeaten.wav</asset>
<asset>carrot.png</asset>
<asset>drop2death.wav</asset>
<asset>eatbeast.wav</asset>
<asset>eatcarrot.wav</asset>
<asset>hawk.png</asset>
<asset>lion.png</asset>
<asset>littleRabbit.mp3</asset>
<asset>passgame.wav</asset>
<asset>rabbit.png</asset>
<asset>snake.png</asset>
<asset>super_rabbit.png</asset>
<asset>superrabbit.mp3</asset>
<asset>tiger.png</asset>
<asset>wolf.png</asset>
</assets>
<apkFile>super_bunny.apk</apkFile>
<info>
<english>This is a super rabbit game. It has four levels. Player can control the rabbit jumping direction by dragging and gliding finger or mouse. However, because of the gravity, the rabbit always jumps more downward than moving direction of finger (or mouse). When the rabbit jumps from the left cliff, it has to avoid the carnivores. However, when the rabbit arrives at the right cliff, it turns to a super rabbit and can eat the carnivores. After the super rabbit jumps back, player passes one level. This game's source code is super_bunny.mfps. It also includes several sound files and image files. If player wants to share source code of this game, the source file and accessories will be packed into a zip file and sent by email.</english>
<simplified_chinese>这是一个超级小白兔的游戏。它有四关。玩家通过滑动手指或鼠标来控制小白兔跳动的方向，但要注意，由于重力的缘故，小白兔跳动的方向相对于手指或鼠标滑动的方向总是偏下。当小白兔从左边的悬崖开始起跳的时候，需要避免跳到食肉动物的格子里被吃掉，但是当小白兔跳到右边悬崖后吃到胡萝卜就会变成超级小白兔，它向回跳时，就能够吃食肉动物。当超级小白兔跳回左边悬崖，玩家就通过了这一关。本游戏的源代码位于文件super_bunny.mfps中。此外，本游戏还包括若干个声音和图像文件。如果玩家共享本游戏的代码，游戏相关文件会被打入一个压缩包中通过email发给别人。</simplified_chinese>
<traditional_chinese>這是一個超級小白兔的遊戲。它有四關。玩家通過滑動手指或鼠標來控制小白兔跳動的方向，但要注意，由於重力的緣故，小白兔跳動的方向相對於手指或鼠標滑動的方向總是偏下。當小白兔從左邊的懸崖開始起跳的時候，需要避免跳到食肉動物的格子裡被吃掉，但是當小白兔跳到右邊懸崖後吃到胡蘿蔔就會變成超級小白兔，它向回跳時，就能夠吃食肉動物。當超級小白兔跳回左邊懸崖，玩家就通過了這一關。本遊戲的源代碼位於文件super_bunny.mfps中。此外，本遊戲還包括若干個聲音和圖像文件。如果玩家共享本遊戲的代碼，遊戲相關文件會被打入一個壓縮包中通過email發給別人。</traditional_chinese>
<spanish>Este es un juego super conejo. Tiene cuatro niveles. El jugador puede controlar la dirección del salto del conejo arrastrando y deslizando el dedo o el ratón. Sin embargo, debido a la gravedad, el conejo siempre salta más hacia abajo que la dirección de movimiento del dedo (o el ratón). Cuando el conejo salta desde el acantilado izquierdo, tiene que evitar los carnívoros. Sin embargo, cuando el conejo llega al acantilado derecho, se convierte en un super conejo y puede comer los carnívoros. Después de que el super conejo salta hacia atrás, el jugador pasa un nivel. El código fuente de este juego es super_bunny.mfps. También incluye varios archivos de sonido y archivos de imagen. Si el jugador quiere compartir el código fuente de este juego, el archivo fuente y los accesorios se incluirán en un archivo zip y se enviarán por correo electrónico.</spanish>
</info>
</example>
